

DAPHNE **SMIT**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

zakelijk.daphne.smit@gmail.com

www.daphnesmit.nl

FOLLOW ME

in LinkedIn

Github

Instagram

Website

LANGUAGE

DUTCH • • • • • • • FRENCH • • • • •



ABOUT ME

My Name Is Daphne Smit, a passionate Freelance Frontend Developer based in Amsterdam.

I am a Front-end Developer with an Interaction Design background and professional working experience since 2010.

I love and live digital. Coffee code repeat.
I am a Big fan of open source and proud creator of: https://www.npmjs.com/package/use-cornify



WORKING EXPERIENCE

> DEPT AGENCY - FRONTEND DEVELOPER APR 2014 - MAR 2020

Dept is an international digital agency with offices around the world. Helping reinvent & accelerate their clients digital reality by creating experience s that people want and businesses need. www.deptagency.com From medior frontend developer I grew to a lead/principal position.

> ICEMOBILE - FRONTEND DEVELOPER

NOV 2013 - OCT 2014

IceMobile was founded in 2002 with the vision that mobile would become the most important medium in people's lives. I was responsible for creating The Bright Admin Console to manage saving digital stamps.

> MATTMO - FE DEVELOPER / INT.DESIGN

FEB 2010 - OCT 2013

Small design studio in the heart of Amsterdam



EDUCATION

> HOGESCHOOL VAN AMSTERDAM - BSC

2006 - 2010

Communication & Multimedia Design, Interactive Media

> UTRECHT UNIVERSITY

2004 - 2005

Information & Communication sciences



SKILLS

HTML/CSS/SCSS	• • • •	VUEJS	•	•	•	•	•
REACTJS	• • • •	ANGULAR	•	•	•	•	
ES6/JAVASCRIPT	• • • •	TYPESCRIPT	•	•	•	•	•
NEXTJS	• • • •	WEBPACK, ETC	•	•	•	•	•
GIT	• • • •	AZURE DEVOPS	•	•	•	•	•